CHARLESLEXCEL MENDOZA

Q Catalunan Grande, Davao City, 8000

+639062913082

itscharlesm@gmail.com



CAREER OVERVIEW

Hard-working and self-motivated individual with excellent technological skills. An individual with much room for development in every aspect, an individual equipped with different basic skills through experience and perseverance, and lastly, a person with a good character.

EDUCATION

Primary

Saint Francis Xavier Learning Center

Senior High School

University of Immaculate Conception

College

BS Computer Science University of Mindanao

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

COMMUNICATION

 Able to understand, read, and speak English language

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel
- · Slide presentations
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript
- Laravel Framework
- Java
- Python
- Flutter

PROGRAMMING PROJECTS

- Belens Beauty Parlor Management System | School Project | Vanilla PHP
- Annimunity | School Project | Flutter
- Hazard Payroll | DOST XI | Laravel Framework
- Enrollment System CQA Review Center | Laravel Framework

- Bookstore Management System | CQA Review Center | Laravel Framework
- Learning Management System | CQA Review
 Center | Laravel Framework
- Forms Management System | Advance Infinit Technology Solutions Incorporated | Laravel Framework
- Point of Sale System | Alexian Brothers | Laravel Framework
- Research and Publication System | University of Mindanao | Laravel Framework

EXPERIENCE

- Service Crew Hitolicious Restaurant | January 2016 January 2017
- Freelance Encoder 8 Spatial | January 2021 March 2023
- Intern Web Programmer Department of Science and Technology Reginal Office no. XI | June 2023 - August 2023
- Chat Support INCOMATION | April 2023 October 2023
- Advisor Concentrix Corporation | October 2023 -February 2024
- Full-stack Web Developer Advanced Infinit Technology Solutions Incorporated | June 2024 -Present

TRAININGS/ SEMINARS/ ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Code Your Future: 40 Mins Coding Workshop for Non-Coders in partnership with DICT Region XI and University of Mindanao | March 22, 2023
- Information Technology Specialist in Databases | Certiport — A PeasonVUE Business | June 13, 2023
- Information Technology Specialist in HTML and CSS | Certiport — A PeasonVUE Business | June 15, 2023
- Dean's Lister University of Mindanao | S.Y. 2020-2024
- Magna Cum Laude University of Mindanao | August 5, 2024